Opening
A Kind Person
Stop! The paint is still wet, so don’t touch.
The Kitten’s Lullaby
Okay.
Those have broken too?
It’d probably be better to buy new ones.
They can still be fixed.
There’s no reason to buy new ones.
How’s college?
Nothing special.
Are you going?
Are you getting all your credits?
Of course.
That’s good.
Fujimoto-kun, you do nothing but work all the time.
Good morning, Kobato-chan.
Good morn…
Kobato-chan fell down again!
Geez, you’re such a klutz!
Are you all right, Kobato-chan?
Geez…
How come you always fall down
when there’s nothing in your way?
Ow…
Thank you very much.
Fujimoto-san!
I’m going to help you. Please let me help!
If you want to…
Yes!
Umm, Fujimoto-san…
There’s something I’d like to ask you about.
Fujimoto-san?
Stop it. Just keep moving your hands.
If you have time to talk, then you aren’t busy enough.
Okay…
What is it?
Yes?
What did you want to ask me?
Oh? Yes.
Um, it’s about the strange call from the other day.
Why can’t we tell Sayaka-sensei about it?
We just can’t.
But why can’t we?
If you can’t keep quiet about it, then don’t come here anymore.
If you tell her, she'll suffer for it... That’s why.
Sayaka-sensei will… suffer?
Do you want to help or do you just want to get in the way? Which is it?
What’s wrong, Kobato-chan?
I made Fujimoto-san mad again.
Made him mad?
Yes.
All I do is get in the way of Fujimoto-san’s work.
Then you should apologize.
We can go apologize together.
I’m sure he only got angry
because he’s worried about you.
I wonder if that‘s true.
Of course it is!
Cheer up!
He’s angry because he wants you to be a good kid. That’s what my Mama always says.
Yes, of course. If I apologize, I think he’ll let me help again.
Huh?
He’s not here.
I wonder what this is.
Ah, this is probably Fujimoto-kun’s report.
Report?
I wonder if he needs it today…
Could you take it to him for me?
Me?
He’ll be in trouble without it.
I’ll take it to him!
What’s going on? You’re in a good mood today.
I want to show him that I don’t always get in the way, that I even can be useful sometimes.
The university that Fujimoto-san attends is around here, right?
Didn’t you listen to the directions carefully?
Yes!
But what’s a university?
You didn’t know something like that, yet you went anyway?
I guess I shouldn’t be surprised by your lack of common knowledge anymore.
A university is where you engage in all sorts of difficult studies.
Studies?
Yeah.
Like things you want to do or if there’s a job you want.
Things you want to do?
People… there are so many people!
It’s a university, of course there’ll be many people.
I wonder how many Yomogi Preschools this makes?
You can’t compare that!
Just look for him.
Yes, Ioryogi-san!
Um…
E-Excuse me!
Eh… um… oh?
Don’t get lost!
We couldn’t find Fujimoto-san.
You walked aimlessly around the campus, of course we couldn’t find him!
I’m going to do my best!
Huh?
It’s Fujimoto-san.
Why are you just standing there?
That’s right! If I don’t give this to him…
You’re going to fall down again!
I’m sorry. Are you all right?
Yes.
Me too! I’m so sorry.
Don’t worry about it, I’m fine.
It’s a cute stuffed animal. Here.
Thank you very much.
This is… Are you a friend of Kiyokazu?
No!
No, we’re not friends but…
You want to see him?
Yeah, probably.
Me too.
Who are you?
Oh, I’m Doumoto Takashi. And you are?
Nice to meet you! I’m Hanato Kobato!
I came to bring Fujimoto-san something he had forgotten.
Fujimoto-san!
He was here just a second ago...
Looks like he escaped.
I made him mad earlier.
Again?
“Again?”
He gets mad really easily.
But it’s because I’m always messing things up.
But I think he gets way too mad at me.
But I’m always at fault. It’s never his fault.
Oh, from Yomogi Preschool.
Yes! I’m helping out there.
Well, let’s look for Kiyokazu together, Kobato-chan.
For Fujimoto-san? Is that okay?
Would I be in the way?
No, not at all. You’d be a big help.
That’s good.
At this time, he’s probably in the Legal Philosophy class.
It’s all right. He’ll be on campus all day today.
He finally took a day off from work.
Is that so?
It’s almost exam time.
Fujimoto-san always seems so busy.
That’s true.
He doesn’t take all the classes he wants because work comes first.
But that’s just like Kiyokazu, isn’t it?
Doumoto-kun! We have a request.
Is something wrong?
We want your help.
We don’t know where to start on Professor Hayakawa’s report.
And suddenly we only have until next week. Isn’t that terrible?
I get it, I get it. Okay.
Yay!
Thank you, Doumoto-kun!
Even if I help, the work still has to be your own.
We understand!
We’ll be in your care.
Oh well.
So, let’s go.
Fujimoto? I haven’t seen him.
Maybe he’s at the library?
Thanks. If you see him, could you tell him I’m looking for him?
Impossible.
He’s not very sociable and he’s kinda scary.
Not really.
Anyway, he’s really difficult.
Is everyone scared of Fujimoto-san?
He’s not very sociable because he always looks angry.
How about you, Doumoto-san?
Huh?
Earlier, you said you made him mad.
Kiyokazu has his reasons for being angry.
For a long time, he was the type who needed everyone’s help.
But I sort of gave him some advice on his future.
I knew I shouldn’t have said it, but I did anyway.
Why?
Huh?
Well, I guess because I just can’t leave him be.
Sayaka-sensei!
What is it?
Everyone’s waiting.
Hurry and come play!
I’m sorry. Fujimoto-kun and Kobato-chan are both gone today, so it’s boring, right?
Oh, ah, not really.
Just wait a bit longer.
Sayaka-sensei!
It’s a guest!
Good afternoon!
It’s Chiho-san and Chise-san!
Chitose, what’s wrong?
You see…
The three of us made macarons.
So we thought we’d share with everyone.
Right?
My…
Itadakimasu!
Yummy!
They’re so crispy!
Sayaka, where are Kiyokazu-kun and Kobato-san?
Today, both of them are at the university.
Kobato-san too?
Fujimoto? He just left.
I see. Thanks.
We’ll try looking elsewhere.
Doumoto.
You get along with Professor Tomita, right?
It’ll be bad if I can’t get the credits this year.
Could you talk to him for me?
Have you tried yourself?
No, it’d feel awkward.
It’d be better if you did first…
I understand. I’ll put in a word.
Really? I owe you one.
But you’ll have to talk to the Professor too.
Everyone really relies on Doumoto-san, right, Ioryogi-san?
Okay, I got it. Thanks!
Kobato-chan.
Sorry for the wait.
It’s all right.
Could we stop by somewhere?
Ah, yes.
Even if you ask, there aren’t any seats left.
It’s been really worrying him.
Please think about it, Professor Tomita.
I understand, but only because you asked.
Thank you so much.
Sorry for the wait.
Doumoto-san, you’re amazing.
Amazing? How so?
Many people rely on you and you help them a lot too.
Really?
Yes.
I want to be helpful to everyone but there isn’t much I can do.
That’s why you’re amazing, Doumoto-san.
I wonder if I should thank you or not…
Huh?
It’s nothing. Shall we go?
Yes.
It’s a tie!
Ah, I lost!
Chiho-chan’s it!
Okay everyone, let’s go hide!
One… two…
Is that so? That’s why she went to the university.
Kobato-chan is very energetic.
It’s so like her.
Sayaka, could you look at this?
Yukari-chan.
Chise-chan?
Which one?
Yukari-chan, I got you!
You were Chiho-chan?
This is from someone who is
able to discuss your financing.
This is from an accountant I know.
And this is…
Sorry, Chitose.
Sayaka, do you understand?
I’m not helping you out of pity.
I want to protect Yomogi Preschool
because Chiho, Chise and I all went here.
So you shouldn’t apologize.
Thank you.
Finally, there he is.
What’s with that?
You’re skipping class, aren’t you?
I don’t want to help people like that.
Why? If you don’t want to help
people, you should just say that.
Well then, I don’t want to. I refuse.
Fine then!
We shouldn’t have asked him anyway.
What are you doing here?
Fujimoto-san, you’re terrible!
What is it?
You didn’t have to be so mean to them!
Saying those things just to make them mad!
That’s not it. They were just trying to cheat again.
Those people could have had
circumstances we didn’t know about.
It doesn’t matter. Mind your own business.
You forgot this. I brought it for you.
Kobato…
I can’t believe I said something like that…
Kobato-chan.
Doumoto-san.
Oh, I forgot to thank you for
helping me look for Fujimoto-san.
Um, I’m sorry.
Oh, sit down.
How long have you known Kiyokazu?
Um, since this spring.
I see.
What’s the matter?
I was just a bit jealous…
Huh?
…of you and Kiyokazu.
Of me and Fujimoto-san?
I’ve known him longer but I
can’t talk to him like you did.
I think I must have really hurt him.
I said some really rude things.
No, you weren’t wrong.
What you said was right.
But I can never tell him the truth like that.
Sorry, I’m being too wishful.
But there are many other wonderful things about you, Doumoto-san.
Like your kindness.
I’m not really that kind.
Eh? But listening to everyone’s requests
and then using your power to help is kind.
About that,
it’s just difficult for me to refuse.
I still think about others but the truth is,
I really should turn them down like Kiyokazu does.
You’re skipping class, aren’t you?
I don’t want to help people like that.
Kiyokazu is not afraid of being hated. He’s a strong person.
The people around him keep away because he displays such strength.
I’m jealous of that strength.
Jealous of his strength?
Yeah.
I don’t know very much about Fujimoto-san...
...but being scary must be lonely.
It must be tough having people hate you.
The people we met today, you helped them.
They looked so happy.
But that’s-
Doumoto-san!
Is it wrong to not want to be hated?
Is it wrong to want the love of others?
Is it wrong to simply help people?
Is it wrong to want to do something for those who are in trouble?
I can’t say it well, but…
You’re a good person.
Thanks.
Huh?
You’re a curious girl.
D-Did I say something weird?
Because I don’t know anything, I’m always making Ioryogi-san angry.
Ioryogi-san?
Yes! Ioryogi-san is a stuffed animal but he can talk!
He can talk but I’m not allowed to speak to him!
Hey!
That stuffed animal is Ioryogi-san?
Yes!
Doumoto-kun!
From before…
Well, I guess…
Yes! Thank you very much!
I should be thanking you. See you later.
Yes.
Eh?!
Why is there more confetti?
It’s because you appreciated how kind that stud muffin is.
“Stud muffin”… You mean Doumoto-san?
Was there anyone else?
But, I got confetti just for appreciating him?
If it’s what the other person is looking for.
Really?
Well, stud muffins also have their own problems.
By the way, Dobato…
About this afternoon…
Yes?
Why did you tell him about me?!
But I did as you said and didn’t talk to you!
Nobody would believe in a talking stuffed animal or talking to a stuffed animal!
I’m so sorry!
Kobato…
30 points!
Ehh!
No way!
Huh?
I’m just saying, you were a lifesaver.
Oh, Fujimoto-kun. The same as always.
He really is awkward.
That was him, thanking you with all his heart.
Thanking me?
Kobato-chan! Kiyokazu-sensei isn’t mad anymore, right?
He’s not scary. He’s really nice.
Yeah, he is. When I lost the
key to my house, he found it.
And he made me a bamboo dragonfly!
And he gave me a cicada shell.
He’s not a bad person.
What a strange person, Fujimoto-san is.